I am cool brother friend thank you
yes this is in the bag its engine volume minimum
four stroke single cylinder OHP sheet this is the
note cross I have collected along with it there is
no chance of weight and rain SMS this is it
then brother its insurance is also for next five
years no tension no worries china
jhal brother you know all this still you are having a
big misconception this
part light insurance of yours is third
party insurance which covers others
but the insurance which covers your damage and fat will
expire after just one year do not
forget to renew it every year
ah
yes brother
sweet you also do not remain in this misconception and get your
two wheeler insurance policy renewed every year from ICICI Lombard
and avail all the good services like our
wide network boxer garage and inspector